themesandmods.com 2017-12-14

# Privacy Policy, Terms and Conditions

## [ Privacy Policy ](http://www.themesandmods.com/privacy-policy/ "Permanent Link to Privacy Policy")

This website routinely collects information about its visitors, subscribers, members, and customers. This information is obtained in various ways, such as:

 **Registration:** Registration means that you submit the information by filling out a form, respond to a survey, send or respond to an email, uploading or downloading a file.

 **Email Inquires:** Website visitors who wish to communicate with the website do so under two conditions: one, they give their permission for contact by the website; two, they are subject to any ‘submission’ provisions of the Terms of Use, or this Privacy Policy. While your email address may or may not be used to solicit you, it is added to the website’s general solicitation database.

 **Visitor Email or Testimonials:** If you are a visitor and send an email to the website, or if you communicate with the site by phone or mail, the website collects information about your communication and by communicating with the site you give your permission to collect, archive, retrieve, and otherwise use any information collected as the site sees fit.

Any communication which, in its sole discretion, the site deems to be a testimonial, may be publicized for commercial purposes.

 **Site Advertisers:** Visitors clicking on banners or hyperlinked advertising appearing on this website must assume that information is being collected about them. This site is not responsible for the use of information collected in such a fashion. Visitors must assume that (1) information will be collected, (2) that ‘cookies’ will usually be placed on their hard drive, (3) that ThemesAndMods.com does not have any control over what happens with this information, (4) that ThemesAndMods.com takes no responsibility over the accuracy or content of advertisers, (5) that ThemesAndMods.com is not responsible for downloads from third party advertisers that contain viruses, worms, malwares, trojans or other computer code that causes their computer or software harm, and (6) that ThemesAndMods.com assumes no responsibility for the data that is garnered from the click itself or that the advertiser collects.

 **Surveys and/or Ratings:** Unless otherwise specified, you must assume that any information provided to the website as part of a survey and/or rating in which you participate may be used for general solicitation for commercial purposes and that such information will be shared with joint venture partners, affiliates, marketing organization or used by the site itself for product design or solicitation purposes.

 **Cookies:** You must assume that your web-viewing or web-use activity is monitored, tracked, and information collected. ‘Cookies’ are bits of computer code placed on your hard drive. Websites use this to keep you ‘logged in’, to keep track of search criteria, to monitor use, to password protect use of the site or use of materials on the site. Cookies can also be used to obtain information about your computer configuration or your use of your computer. The information about you may or may not be personal information, but it is information and by using this site you are expressly giving permission to use ‘cookies’ and to use the information gathered from their use to improve service to you.

 **INFORMATION USE**

While actual use of any information collected may be used quite conservatively, you must assume that it is not. You must assume that information collected is shared with other persons or entities for commercial purposes. While this is uncommon in practice, you must assume that it is as you make your decision whether or not to view or interact with this website. This type of shared information may include your name, email address and your site url, as well as other information. This information may be used for general commercial solicitation by this website or other persons it is sold to, rented to, or shared with.

 **Email:** By providing to this website information that forms the basis of communication with you, such as an email address, you waive all rights to file complaints concerning unsolicited email or spam from this website since, by providing such information, you agree to receive communication from us or other marketing organizations. However, all email communication with you shall contain an ‘unsubscribe’ link where you may notify the website that you no longer wish to receive solicitations or information from the website and your name will be removed from the general solicitation database.

 **Data Security:** This website takes measures to protect its data that contains information related to you. However, as a consideration for viewing this site or interacting with this site in any manner, you waive all claims of any nature against this site concerning the loss, alteration, or misuse of information. You must assume that it is possible for your personal data to be obtained by others, such as ‘hackers,’ and used in an inappropriate manner that may cause you harm and that you agree that the site is not responsible for damages to you.

 **TERMS & CONDITIONS:**

When visiting ThemesAndMods.com, visitors agree to the Terms of Service as mentioned on this page. We reserve the right to update, revise or append the Terms of Service at any time by posting such modifications for public view.

 **External Links:** ThemesAndMods.com has affiliated links to other websites. We are not responsible for those website’s contents or their privacy practices.

 **Statement of Liability and Basic Disclaimer:** All products, services, information and content is furnished to you “as is” with none guaranteed. ThemesAndMods.com will not assume liability for any damages (including residual, special, consequential or indirect) that may result from the use of the materials provided through the use of this website, even if ThemesAndMods.com has previously been informed that the potential for such damages exist.

 **Trademarks and Copyrights:** Info inside this web site is copyrighted by ThemesAndMods.com, besides in circumstances the place photographs, functions or text is dually licensed and accepted from affiliates or third-party vendors.

 **Contacting Us:**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us using our [contact form](http://www.themesandmods.com/contact/ "Contact Us").

#### About

We are dedicated to provide best collection of feature rich ready made website designs and extensions for various content management systems and ecommerce solutions. We do our best to keep the site fresh and updated with the latest designs. Around 8000 designs have been added to our collection so far. Keep watching for more updates. And, please do support us by purchasing your favorite templates and plugins through our website.

#### Sign up for our email newsletters

#### Follow Us

© 2017, Themes & Mods
